Finding Aid for the Jesse Ely Wills Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Outgoing Correspondence Index
  - Thomas Daniel Young, 25 September, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Thomas Daniel Young, 29 September, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alexander Heard, 30 September, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - William H. Vanderbilt, 20 October, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Robert Penn Warren, 21 October, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Andrew Benedict, James G. Stahlman, 28 October, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Members of the Trust Committee on Academic Programs of Vanderbilt University, 29 October, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Nancy Jane Manning, 29 October, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Mrs. Mapheus Smith, 13 December, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Alexander Heard, William S. Vaughn, 13 January, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Robert McGaw, 15 January, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Robert McGaw, Mrs. Mapheus Smith, 15 January, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Goldle D. Hirsch, 19 January, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - William S. Vaughn, 27 January, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Forrest Read, 29 January, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Charlie Ragland, 4 February, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Andrew Lytle, Robert Penn Warren, 5 February, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Nicholas Hobbs, 5 February, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - William Waller, 9 February, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Eldon Stevenson, 9 February, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Mrs. Albert Werthan, 16 February, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Mrs. Albert Werthan and Norfleet H. Rand, 16 February, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Alexander Heard, 19 February, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - William H. Vanderbilt, Charles Ragland, 19 February, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Allen Tate, 2 March, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Norfleet H. Rand, 16 March, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Charles S. Ragland, 17 March, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Allen Tate, 23 March, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alexander Heard, 25 March, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Alexander Heard, 26 March, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Members of the Trust Committee on Academic Programs of Vanderbilt University, 26 March, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Members of the Trustee Committee on Academic Programs of Vanderbilt University, 22 April, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Matt Wigginton, 27 April, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Robert McGaw, 28 April, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Mrs. Merrill Moore, 25 May, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Mrs. Merrill Moore, 9 June, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Allen Tate, William W. Force, 10 June, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - William S. Vaughn, 6 July, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - William Yandell Elliott, 8 July, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Mrs. Harold S. Vanderbilt, 9 July, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Merrimon Cuninggim, 22 July, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Maxey Jarman, 17 August, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Margaret Williams, 20 August, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - William S. Vaughn, 14 September, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Nicholas Hobbs, William Waller, Merrimon Cuninggim, 17 September, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - William Waller, 21 October, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - William Waller, 26 October, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Alexander Heard, 11 November, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Vernon Sharp, 12 November, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Robert L. Garner, 18 November, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Allen Tate, John Crowe Ransom, 30 November, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Jean and Alexander Heard, 14 December, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Thomas D. Young, 23 December, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Randolph Batson, 16 January, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Robert A. McGaw, 18 January, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Matthew B. Wills, 20 January, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Robert Sturdivant, Aubrey Harwell, 20 January, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Louise Davis, 21 January, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Thomas Daniel Young, Allen Tate, 25 January, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Mrs. Donald Davidson, 1 February, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Jane S. Whitman, 2 February, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Walter R. Courtenay, 2 March, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Edgar H. Duncan, 9 March, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Victor S. Johnson, 15 March, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Archie Henry, 16 March, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Frank P. Grisham, 17 March, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Nicholas Hobbs, 17 March, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Nicholas Hobbs, Members of the Educational Programs Committee, 24 March, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Thomas D. Young, 18 March, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Allen Tate, 7 April, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Chase A. Horton, 27 April, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - David E. Wood, 3 May, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Ralph R. Kirkendall, 5 May, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Donald L. Thistlethwaite, 6 May, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Donald L. Thistlethwaite, 18 May, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - John M. Aden, 19 May, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Robert Pénn Warren, 7 June, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Mrs. Winston Caldwell, 21 June, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Frances Neel Cheney, 22 June, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Allen Tate, 30 June, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alexander Heard, 15 July, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Thomas Daniel Young, 17 July, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Allen Tate, 2 August, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Frank P. Grisham, 3 August, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - William S. Vaughn, 9 August, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - T. H. Hirschfield, 29 September, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - William S. Vaughn, 30 September, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Rob Roy Purdy, 11 October, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Mrs. Mapheus Smith, 11 October, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Rob Roy Purdy, 13 October, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Frank Grisham, 14 October, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Thomas Daniel Young, 1 November, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - William Waller, 15 November, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Rob Roy Purdy, 15 November, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Barry L. Master, 15 November, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - William S. Vaughn, 15 November, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Robert A. McGaw, 16 November, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Frank P. Grisham, 24 November, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Fannie (Mrs. Brainard) Cheney, 29 November, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Thomas Daniel Young, 30 November, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Allen Tate, 9 December, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Frank P. Grisham, 20 December, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Allen Tate, 21 December, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Frank P. Grisham, 31 December, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Frederick J. Dockstader, n.d. December, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Thomas Daniel Young, 24 January, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Andrew Lytle, 25 January, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Herschel Gower, 3 February, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Mrs. Brainard Cheney, Frank P. Grisham, 16 February, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Rob Roy Purdy, 21 February, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - David Spencer Taber, 28 February, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - William F. Orr, 14 March, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Rob Roy Purdy, Harris D. Riley, Jr., 20 March, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Robert E. Weaver, 23 March, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Nicholas Hobbs, 4 April, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Nicholas Hobbs, 4 April, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Nicholas Hobbs, 6 April, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Nicholas Hobbs, 26 April, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Nicholas Hobbs, 8 May, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Allen Tate, 1 May, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allen Tate, Mrs. Hugh Bullock, 8 May, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Thomas Daniel Young, 16 May, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Mrs. Richmond C. Beatty, 12 June, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Mrs. Richmond C. Beatty, 15 June, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Allen Tate, Thomas Daniel Young, 21 June, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Frank K. Houston, 29 June, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Thomas Daniel Young, 8 August, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Thomas Daniel Young, 6 September, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Robert A. McGaw, 14 September, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - H.L. Swint, 20 September, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Robert Penn Warren, 9 October, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Thomas Daniel Young, 10 October, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Frank P. Grisham, Robert Penn Warren, 30 October, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Robert Penn Warren, 21 November, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Rob Roy Purdy, 14 December, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Robert A. McGaw, 18 December, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Members of the Committee on Academic Programs, n.d., 1972 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Allen Tate, 5 March, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Andrew Lytle, 22 March, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Robert A. McGaw, 11 June, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allen Tate, 7 August, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Frank P. Grisham, 9 August, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Andrew Lytle, 28 August, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Earvie Branscomb, 18 September, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - E. Bronson Ingram, 19 September, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - E. Bronson Ingram, 25 September, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Allen Tate, 26 September, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Rupert E. Palmer, Jr., 1 October, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Robert Penn Warren, 29 October, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Walter Harrelson, 21 November, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - William C. Pratt, 3 December, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Robert Penn Warren, 6 December, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Walter Harrelson, 2 January, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Allen Tate, 2 January, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Daniel T. Young, 3 January, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allen Tate, 8 January, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Mrs. Eric Bell, Jr., 14 January, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Mr. and Mrs. W.A. Baker, 15 January, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Frank P. Grisham, Rupert Palmer, 21 January, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allen Tate, 23 January, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allen Tate, 24 January, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allen Tate, 29 January, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Allen Tate, 20 February, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allen Tate, 4 March, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allen Tate, Marice Wolfe, 6 March, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - John W. Poindexter, 25 March, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Andrew Lytle, 1 April, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allen Tate, 3 April, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alexander Heard, 6 April, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Daniel T. Young, 10 July, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Robert A. McGaw, 11 July, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Daniel T. Young, 22 July, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Frank P. Grisham, Mrs. Alexander Heard, 24 July, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Thomas Daniel Young, 29 July, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allen Tate, 31 July, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allen Tate, 1 August, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allen Zibart, 14 August, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allen Tate, 15 August, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allen Tate, 4 September, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allen Tate, 9 September, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Edwin Stirling, Allen Tate, 18 September, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allen Tate, 1974: 25 September, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dr. and Mrs. T.E. Brittingham, 7 October, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Scott Colley, 14 October, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Edwin Sterling, 31 October, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Frank Grisham, 6 November, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Frank Grisham, Allen Tate, 18 November, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allen Tate, 4 December, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - M.S. Wigginton, Andres B. Benedict, Jr., John Bransford, 9 December, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Emily Bennett, 16 December, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allen Tate, 17 December, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - John E. Sloan, Jr., 23 December, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Rob Roy Purdy, 6 January, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Allen Tate, 15 January, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - John Scott Colley, Frank Grisham, 21 January, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Allen Tate, 23 January, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Robert A. McGaw, 9 February, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Robert Penn Warren, 10 February, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Allen Tate, 12 February, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Allen Tate, 3 April, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - T. Daniel Young, 14 April, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Rob Roy Purdy, 17 April, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - O.B. Emerson, 21 April, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Rob Roy Purdy, 2 June, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Robert A. McGaw, 10 June, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Rob Roy Purdy, 24 June, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Allen Tate, 26 June, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Helen Tate, 7 July, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Rob Roy Purdy, 9 July, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Robert A. McGaw, 16 July, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Gus G. Halliburton, 9 September, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Robert Penn Warren, 15 September, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Robert A. McGaw, 22 September, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Rob Roy Purdy (2), T. Daniel Young, 6 October, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Rob Roy Purdy, Allen Tate, 27 October, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - T.D. Young, 5 November, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Rob Roy Purdy, 17 November, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Caroline Gordon, 16 December, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Caroline Gordon, 6 January, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - John Hall Wheelock, 13 January, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Lon (Brainard) Cheney, 19 January, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Mrs. Buford Sanders, 12 February, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Mrs. J.R. Hamblen, 16 February, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Mrs. Caroline Gordon Tate, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Rob Roy Purdy, 1 March, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Allen Tate, 8 April, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Robert A. McGaw, 13 April, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Frank P. Grisham, Robert A. McGaw, 3 May, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Sam M. Fleming, T. Daniel Young, 17 May, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - William Boozer, 18 May, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bob A. McGaw, 1 June, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Robert A. McGaw, 17 June, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Frank P. Grisham, 26 July, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Frank P. Grisham, 29 July, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Allen Tate, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - George Core, 2 September, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Marilyn W. Whiteman, Allen Tate, 10 September, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Rob Roy Purdy, 20 September, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Robert A. McGaw, 27 September, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alexander Heard, 18 October, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Frank P. Grisham, 4 November, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Robert Penn Warren, 10 January, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Memorandum on Fugitive Room in the New Wing of the Joint University Library, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 6)